Once upon a time in Nazi occupied France...
Inglourious Basterds is a drama, thriller, war
film directed by Quentin Tarantino.
In Nazi-occupied France during World War II, a group of Jewish-American soldiers known as "The Basterds" are
chosen specifically to spread fear throughout the Third Reich by scalping and brutally killing Nazis.
The Basterds, lead by Lt.
Aldo Raine soon cross paths with a French-Jewish teenage girl who runs a
movie theater in Paris which is targeted by the soldiers.
LT. Aldo Raine, played by Brad Pitt.
Shosanna, played by Mélanie Laurent.
COL. Hans Landa, played by Christoph Waltz.
SGT. Donny Donowitz, played by Eli Roth.
LT. Archie Hicox, played by Michael Fassbender.
Bridget von Hammersmark, played by Diane Kruger.
Quentin Tarantino's Inglourious Basterds: Motion Picture Soundtrack is the
soundtrack to Quentin Tarantino's motion picture Inglourious Basterds.
It was originally released on August 18, 2009.
The soundtrack uses a variety of music genres, including Spaghetti Western soundtrack
excerpts, R&B and a David Bowie song from the 1982 remake of Cat People.
"The Man with the Big Sombrero", a song from the 1943 screwball comedy Hi
Diddle Diddle, was rerecorded in French for the movie.
This is the first soundtrack for a Quentin Tarantino
film not to feature dialogue excerpts.
The album was nominated for a Grammy Award for Best Compilation Soundtrack Album for a Motion
Picture, Television or Other Visual Media, but lost to the Slumdog Millionaire soundtrack.
The film explores themes of guerrilla warfare, paris, france,
self sacrifice, world war ii, jew persecution.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.